Steven Dismuke

Web Developer

Summary

Web developer keen on learning new technologies and languages. Prior to web development I worked as a math department head for a private school where I taught and managed curriculum across multiple grade levels. I also assisted in starting up Houston Barbecue Company as technical support.

Skils

Javascript, Python, Node.js, React, Express, Redux, PostgreSQL, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, GitHub

Education

Digital Crafts December | 2019

Full-Stack Immersive Program

University of Wyoming | 2017-2019

B.S. Mechanical Engineering | Incomplete

Daniel Webster College | 2013

B.S. in Air Traffic Management and Business FAA CTI program

St. Johnsbury Academy| 2003

High School Diploma

Contact

Email: <u>stevelp99@gmail.com</u> **GitHub:** <u>github.com/stevelp99</u>

Linkedin: <u>linkedin.com/in/stevendismuke</u> **Portfolio:** stevelp99.github.io/portfolio

Experience

Capstone Academy Katy,TX | 2015-2017

Department Head Mathematics

Developed and implement curriculum across grades 9-12, and college prep. Taught and test students according to institution guidelines. Consulted with parents and students to develop plans to accomplish student goals. Maintain grade records and report quarterly.

Houston Barbecue Company, Lakebriar Holdings LLC, Houston, TX | 2013 – current Technology Coordinator

Maintained all company technology platforms, including networking, computer systems, POS systems, AV installations, and security systems. Budgeted, ordered, and setup company equipment. Diagnosed, troubleshoot system issues and provided recommendations and solutions as needed. Alongside these duties I managed day to day activities including customer service.